翻译  痒痒和他的小跟班儿
翻译  某羽
翻译  小蟹
翻译  waterlike
翻译  噎死青春
翻译  某豚
翻译  sakura
翻译  ~某人
翻译  风吹日落
翻译  小饭
时间轴  chance-coco
后期   饿得慌
顾问   老杜
校对   草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第一季  第十三集
人人影视倾情奉献
什么声音
What was that?
水龙头
The faucet.
滴个不停
It wouldn't shut up.
-你昨晚睡着了吗  -没有
- Did you sleep last night? - No.
我会让南茜叫个水管工来
I'll call Nancy and tell her to call a plumber.
你能保证绝对谨慎吗
Absolute discretion. Can I count on that?
-当然  -雷蒙德・塔斯克
- Always. - Raymond Tusk.
总统想让他接任副总统
The President wants to tap him as the new V.P.
-你我必须阻止他  -为什么
- You and I cannot let that happen. - Why not?
因为他三分之一的资产投在核能上
Because a third of his fortune is tied up in nuclear energy.
支持核能的商人进入白宫对桑科不利
Sancorp does not want a pro-nuclear businessman in the White House.
反正市场正在转向天然气
The market is shifting toward natural gas anyway.
但塔斯克想拖住甚至扭转这个倾向
But Tusk wants to stall that shift or reverse it.
副总统没这么大的影响
Vice President doesn't have that kind of influence.
他有  他和沃克关系很近
This one would. He and Walker are very close.
桑科的市场地位下降
And it's in neither of our best interests
对我们都不是什么好事
to seep Sancorp's position in the marketplace diminished.
你要我做什么
What's the ask?
如果塔斯克觉得自己的资产
Tusk won't accept the nomination
有危险就不会接受任命
if he thinks his holdings are at risk.
桑科需要发起一次恶意收购
Sancorp needs to initiate a hostile takeover.
他的资产顶三个桑科
He's worth three times what Sancorp is.
我是说那些子公司
I'm talking about the subsidiaries.
搞那些提炼  运输铀的公司就行
We go after the companies that refine and ship the uranium,
-辅助系统  -得了  弗兰克
- the support system that... - Come on, Frank.
要考虑到股东
There's stockholders to take into account,
巨大的财务风险
a huge financial exposure.
我们只需要让他分神
We just need to distract him.
象征性地比划两下  暗示一下还没完
Send a few token salvos and intimate there's more to come.
我只要你和你的客户提一句
All I'm asking is that you speak to your client
看看他们有没有什么愿意考虑的办法
and see if this is something they might be willing to consider.
总统周五就会宣布塔斯克的事
The President announces Tusk on Friday,
所以我们时间不多了
so we don't have a lot of time.
-我会打几个电话  -谢谢  雷米
- I'll make some calls. - Thank you, Remy.
他要是办不成  我就单枪匹马了
If he doesn't deliver, I'm an invader without an army.
他要是办成了  我还有点机会
If he does, I've got a fighting chance.
我只是觉得
I just didn't feel that
我们没法再积极地共事下去了
we could work together constructively any longer.
我觉得这是个正当理由
I think that's a perfectly legitimate reason...
当然是
Of course it is.
但你不能以怀孕为理由开除她
But what you can't do is fire someone for being pregnant.
她是这么说的吗
Is that what she's saying?
科尔女士声称你亲口说
Ms. Cole claims that you said,
我需要员工而不是母亲
quote, "I need employees, not mothers,"
还有  去照顾你的孩子吧
and, quote, "Go focus on your baby."
我能看一眼吗
Can I see that?
一派胡言  我
That's completely false. I...
-我从没说过这些  -她说你有
- I never said that. - She claims you did.
那就是对质了  对吗
It's her word against mine, right?
陪审团格外同情孕妇
Well, juries are very sympathetic with expecting mothers.
这是勒索
This is extortion.
我们不想上法庭  克莱尔
We don't want this going to trial, Claire.
你和你丈夫都是公众人物
You and your husband are public figures.
这会产生不利报道
This will result in some very bad press.
我建议跟他们庭外和解
I suggest we go back to them with a settlement offer.
-我们需要逮捕记录  -没有啊
- We need the arrest record. - There isn't any.
-他们把他放了  -那我们得知道谁放了他
- They let him go. - Then we need to know who got him off.
如果安德伍德参与了的话
If Underwood was involved,
那就是滥用职权和腐败了
we are talking abuse of powers and corruption.
我查过了
I checked.
没有立案  没有存档照  什么也没有
There's no files, no mug shot, nothing.
那我们就得找拦车的警察
Then we need to find the cop who pulled him over,
或者看到他进警局的人
or somebody who saw him come into the station.
但是特区的警察  他们相互照顾
But D.C. Cops... they look after each other.
我们得小心点
We need to be careful.
你在警局有联络人吗
Do you have any sources on the force?
没有能在这种事上信得过的人
Not that I would trust with something like this.
卢卡斯当年是做犯罪版的
You know, Lucas started out on the crime beat.
我去问问他认识谁
I can see if he knows anyone.
-他会帮我们吗  -我不知道
- Would he help us? - I don't know.
-可能吧  -帮对手的忙
- Maybe. - Help out a competitor?
我们  一直有联系
We... stayed in touch.
你逗我呢
You've gotta be kidding me.
这个世界真够乱的
This town is way too incestuous.
我知道这事很大
I know it's a lot to ask.
你跟弗兰克的事我还没想通呢  佐伊
I'm still trying to wrap my head around the affair, Zoe.
如果你能给我介绍个人再为我做担保
If you could just give me a contact and maybe vouch for me...
你是不是故意等到现在才说
Did you wait to bring this up until now
觉得我这会儿不好拒绝
because you thought it'd be harder for me to say no?
-什么意思  -在我们刚上过床...
- What do you mean? - In bed, right after we...
你真以为我会做那种...
You don't actually think I would do something like...
-看起来就是这样  -这是大事  卢卡斯
- It sure seems that way. - This is huge, Lucas.
我在极力避免毁掉我们之间的...
I'm trying to avoid fucking up what we have...
不论是什么  但你却让我很为难
Whatever that is... and you're making it really hard for me.
我恐怕永远都没法不让你为难
I don't know that I'll ever be the kind of person that makes it easy.
我不指望会简单
I'm not looking for easy.
但也别总让我想起他
But I don't need to be reminded of him.
-我没法改变过去  -我知道
- I can't erase what I did. - I know you can't.
但你这就是在摆布我
But this is really fucking manipulative.
你之前说的话是真心的吗
Did you mean what you said the other night?
你可能...
That you probably...
那种话让我不知所措
I don't know what to do when I hear something like that.
所以在去机场的路上才一言不发
That's why I was so quiet when you drove me to the airport.
我当时生气  冲口而出
I was angry. I just blurted it out.
我希望我没说  至少不要那么说
I wish I hadn't. At least not like that.
我不是因为你说了那话而想利用你
I'm not trying to take advantage of you because you did.
-他什么也没说  -你也没问
- He hasn't said a word. - And you haven't brought it up?
我只问他是否还在考虑塔斯克
I just asked him if he was still considering Tusk.
他说是  但想先跟你谈谈
He said yes, but that he wanted to speak to you first. That's it.
真想知道他们聊过没
I wish we knew if they'd spoken at all.
他有专线  我没法追查
Well, he has a private line. I can't track those calls.
-弗兰克  -总统先生
- Frank. - Mr. President.
说说圣路易斯的情况吧
Tell me about St. Louis.
很难看出他在想什么  我尽力试探了
He's a hard man to read. I did my best to probe him,
但还是看不出他的倾向
but I don't think I left any wiser to which way he's leaning.
但我得说
I must say, though,
他无疑是最佳人选
I think he is by far and away the best candidate.
为什么那么说
Why do you say that?
提名一个你了解的人不是更合理吗
Doesn't it make sense for you to nominate someone you know so well?
我不了解他  所以才派你去圣路易斯
I don't know him. That's why I sent you to St. Louis.
抱歉总统先生  我不是那个意思
Forgive me, Mr. President. I didn't mean it that way.
我是说全世界都了解他
I meant that the world knows so well.
你  我  所有人都知道雷蒙德・塔斯克
You, me, everyone knows Raymond Tusk.
他的厉害我们不必多说
We don't need to convince anyone of his worthiness.
但你说他依然很犹豫
But you said he still seems ambivalent?
所以我觉得您应该亲自行动
Which is why I think you should make a personal overture.
请他来白宫
Invite him to the White House.
我不想显得太急切
Well, I don't want to appear desperate.
我赞成弗兰克
I agree with Frank.
请他来  这办法很好
Inviting him is a very good idea.
如果您真想用塔斯克  就跟他同桌共饮
If you're serious about Tusk, you should wine and dine him.
让他觉得自己很特别
Make him feel very special.
我想能为他安排出时间
I'm sure we can find time in the schedule.
让他再考虑几天吧
Let's give him a few more days.
我们时间不够一周了  先生
We have less than a week, sir.
不能迟过周五
I wouldn't wait any later than Friday.
周五可以  先生
We can make Friday work, sir.
好吧  那就看看他能不能来
All right. Well, let's see if he's available.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
-给我你手机  -为什么
- Give me your phone. - Why?
快给我
Just give it to me.
你注意到家里有什么怪事吗
Have you noticed anything weird in here?
东西动地方  或是不见了
Stuff moved around? Anything missing?
-没有  -有人跟踪你吗
- No. - Anyone following you?
你发现什么了
What did you find out?
事情很严重  佐伊
This is serious, Zoe.
涉及到了警察局长
It goes way up, as high as the commissioner.
我跟警队的联络人好说歹说才拿到这个
I had to beg my contact at Metro to give me this.
没有罗素被拦下的记录
No record of Russo getting pulled over,
但他记得有个应召女郎跟罗素一起被捕
but he remembers there was a call girl brought in with Russo.
这是她之前一次被捕的案宗
That's a file on one of her previous arrests.
我调查过警察掩盖案件
I've investigated police cover-ups before.
我持续一年收到死亡威胁
I got death threats for a year.
你愿意担这种风险吗
Are you willing to take that risk?
愿意
Yeah.
要多久
How long?
下次董事会要三周后
The next board of directors meeting is three weeks from now.
太迟了  雷米
That is too late. Remy, look,
总统在一周内就会提名他
the President is gonna nominate Tusk in a week or less.
我敦促斯科特・坎宁汉召集紧急会议
I've urged Scott Cunningham to call a special meeting,
但一时半会儿也办不成啊
but that doesn't happen overnight.
这种事很复杂的
There's a lot of machinery in a corporate attack like this.
我要亲自和斯科特・坎宁汉谈谈
I want to meet Scott Cunningham myself.
我不会安排你们会面  你知道规矩
I'm not sitting you down with Scott. You know the rules.
现在是特殊情况
These are extraordinary circumstances.
弗兰克  桑科的高管
Frank, Sancorp's officers
绝不会跟政客会面
do not meet with politicians, period.
你跟我谈  我转述给斯科特・坎宁汉
You talk to me, I talk to Scott Cunningham,
或是反过来  这是规矩
and vice versa. That's how it works.
好吧  雷米  就按你说的吧
All right, Remy. Whatever you think best.
有消息我会通知你
I'll call you when I know more.
南茜
Nancy!
我所尊重的东西里
Of all the things I hold in high regard,
不包括"规矩"
rules are not one of them.
如果可以直接接触供应商
I will not place my fate solely in the hands of the middleman
我就不会把命运完全交给中间人
if I can go directly to the supplier.
订一张明早去亚特兰大的机票  通知密查姆
Book a flight to Atlanta. Tomorrow morning. Let Meechum know.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
她在弗吉尼亚州的林奇堡长大
She grew up in Lynchburg, Virginia,
就读于洛马高中
went to Lorimer High School
高二时退学
until she dropped out sophomore year,
之后就再没有过公共记录
and then after that, there's no public record.
但这儿只说她在2012年4月
But all it says here is that she was fined $300
因滞留街头被罚款三百元
for loitering on April 2012.
得有个人去趟林奇堡
One of us has to go to Lynchburg.
接触一下她的父母  同学
Parents, classmates,
-和老师  -我去吧
- teachers... - I'll do it.
好吧  那打电话招妓就是我们俩的事了
Okay. Well, then, you and I have to call escort services.
我很乐意帮忙
I'm willing to lend a hand,
但我可不想整天打电话
but not by making cold calls 12 hours a day
然后被妓女纠缠
just to get hung up on by hookers.
她是在哪被捕的
Where was she arrested?
-康涅狄格大街  -2460号
- Connecticut ave. - 2460.
那是当地的一家豪华酒店
That's the address of the district grand hotel.
桑科
我可不喜欢不速之客  弗兰克
I'm not a fan of surprise visits, Frank.
雷米不肯安排我们见面
Remy wouldn't arrange a meeting.
雷米・丹顿的存在  就是让我们不必见面
Remy Danton exists so we don't have to meet.
我必须和你谈谈
I needed to speak with you.
国会的旅行报告
There's a congressional travel report
会记录你来过亚特兰大
that puts you on a trip to Atlanta
而同一天  我中途离开了投资者通报会
the same day I was pulled out of an investors' briefing.
我们一直力图避免这种巧合
Those are the sort of coincidences we want to avoid.
你是在跟投资者说雷蒙德・塔斯克吗
Were you briefing your investors on Raymond Tusk?
密查姆是自己人
Meechum can be trusted.
我为什么要跟他们提塔斯克
Why would I be speaking to them about Tusk?
-我以为雷米告诉过你了  -没有
- I thought Remy filled you in. - No.
他完全没提提名副总统的事吗
He didn't say anything about the vice presidential nomination?
没有  而且我预感我也不想知道
He didn't. And I have a feeling I'd rather not be told.
相信我  你会想知道的
Trust me, you want to know.
我曾面对过陪审团  弗兰克
I've appeared in front of grand juries before, Frank.
能说实话可轻松多了
It's much easier when you can tell the truth.
拜托  别让我不得不撒谎脱身
Please, don't put me in a position where I have to lie.
如果总统对塔斯克言听计从
If Tusk has the President's ear,
这届政府就会
you will see this administration
不再支持天然气  转而支持核能
shift its support toward nuclear energy and away from natural gas.
你得去收购他的子公司和供应商
His subsidiaries and his suppliers, go after them.
弗兰克  谈话该到此为止了
Frank, we should end this conversation right now.
如果让他觉得资产保密委托后
He will not accept the nomination
他将无法对抗面临的威胁
if his assets are in a blind trust
他就不会接受提名了
and he can't fight off the threat.
-别再说了  -斯科特
- Okay, we're done. - Scott...
我一个字都不想再听了
I don't wanna hear another word.
回机场去吧
Go back to the airport.
给今天来亚特兰大找个好理由
Figure out a good reason you needed to be in Atlanta today.
在前面转弯处靠边停吧
You can pull over at the next corner.
我会叫车来接我
I'll have my car pick me up.
-来最后一杯吗  -继续倒
- One last one? - Another.
-要喝点什么吗  -白葡萄酒
- Can I get you something? - White wine.
记在我账上
Put that on my tab.
-谢谢  -荣幸之至
- Thank you. - My pleasure.
很快就不能点单了
They're about to call last call.
没关系  我也不是很能喝
That's all right. I don't have much of a tolerance.
再来一杯吗
One more?
不用  就这样吧
No. I'm good.
你该上楼去睡
You should head upstairs.
我在等你
I was waiting for you.
-那是新的水龙头吗  -是的
- Is that the new faucet? - Yeah.
进展如何
How'd it go?
不是很好  雷米有所企图
Not good. Remy's up to something.
也不回我电话
He's not returning my phone calls.
我能做什么
What can I do?
告诉我你梦到了什么
Tell me what you were dreaming.
很可怕  弗兰西斯
Oh, it was so awful, Francis.
他也让我无法入睡
He's not letting me sleep either.
不是他  是孩子们
Yeah. It's not him. It's the kids.
我跟他们在后院玩
I was playing with them in the backyard,
女孩爬到藤蔓上去了
and the girl was climbing on the vines,
我一直劝她下来...
and I kept telling her to stop and get down, and...
藤蔓突然把她缠住  就是不放开
The vines just took hold of her, and they wouldn't let go.
她厉声尖叫
And she was screaming so loud,
我就一直使劲拉
and I just kept pulling harder and harder,
后来她被撕成两半
and she just ripped in half.
好了  没事了
Come here. Come here. Okay.
天呐
Jesus!
你等到凌晨两点之后才回我电话
You wait until after 2:00 in the morning to return my call?
就想给我留言吧
You trying to get my voice-mail?
我要说的话不能在手机上说
The conversations we're having we can't be having on cell phones.
你在哪
Where are you?
克莱尔在楼上睡觉
Claire is sleeping upstairs.
你不该去见坎宁汉
You shouldn't have gone to see Cunningham.
他说你没有提起塔斯克
He says you didn't bring up Tusk.
你觉得他真会承认吗
You really think he'd admit to that?
如果我们这么做  就是内线交易
If we go through with this, it's insider trading.
我觉得他不是第二次听到这消息
He didn't strike me as a man hearing the news for the second time.
你觉得我在耍你吗
You want to believe I'm playing games?
现在我就抽身而出
I can walk away from the whole thing.
但现在没别人能帮你了
But I'm all you've got right now.
是我在帮你和桑科
I'm the one doing you and Sancorp a favor,
不是反过来
not the other way around.
被利用我还看的出来  弗兰克
I can tell when I'm being used, Frank.
我只想知道为了什么
I just want to know what for.
我不会利用我事后不能甩开的人
I don't use people unless I can throw them away afterwards.
我是在强化我们之间的合作关系
I'm trying to strengthen our partnership.
我觉得你是在骗人
Smells an awful lot like bullshit.
别一副高高在上的口气
Don't condescend.
为你工作八年
Eight years I worked on your staff
我最多也就是站在你家门前
and never once made it further than your front doorstep.
现在我站在你家客厅了  弗兰克
Well, now I'm in your living room, Frank.
不是因为你的教导
It's not because of what you taught me,
而是我终于意识到我的价值
it's because I finally woke up to what my value is
和为你卖命是多么屈才
and how undervalued I was slaving away for you.
这是正事  伤心事自己知道就行
This is business. Keep your sob story to yourself.
我想坚守住
I want to maintain
我在白宫辛苦经营的影响力
the influence that I have worked to achieve in the White House,
这份影响力进而转化为
which translates into the influence
你在白宫的影响力
that you have in the White House,
都是通过我
through me.
我明天再跟斯科特谈谈
I'll get in touch with Scott again tomorrow.
看能不能尽快办妥
See if we can push this forward faster.
谢谢  雷米
Thank you, Remy.
但你得让我按我的方式来
But you gotta let me do this my way.
她说得很清楚
The message was very clear.
她不想和解  无论金额多少
She doesn't want a settlement, no matter what the figure.
即使我们把世界之井还她吗
Even if we give her World Well back?
她坚持要上法庭
She wants to go to court.
他们说下周就会有正式传票
They said we can expect a formal summons next week.
-这太荒唐了  -她律师也这么认为
- This is ludicrous. - Her lawyers agree.
他们也愿意和解  但她不同意
They'd much prefer a settlement too, but she's not playing ball.
我会继续施压  与此同时
I'll keep pushing them. But in the meantime,
你得整理一下
you should start gathering
你们之间所有的通讯
all the correspondence you ever had with her...
电子邮件  笔记  什么都别落下
E-mails, notes, every scrap of paper.
好的  谢谢  奥利弗
Okay. Thanks, Oliver.
我只不过想找到她
All I'm trying to do is find her.
我有份2012年4月她被捕的记录
I've got an arrest record from April 2012,
我知道一月她和一位客户的车被警察拦下
and I know she was pulled over with a client in January.
那个姑娘  她非常有潜力
That girl. She had so much potential.
她为什么辍学
Why did she drop out?
我说过了  由于道德缘故
Like I said, it's an ethical breach for me
我不能透露任何...
to discuss anything that has to do...
我和她父母谈过了
I spoke to her parents.
她父亲态度很横
Her father was very combative.
是家里的问题吗
Was there trouble at home?
父亲  是不是...
The father... did he...
我不会谈瑞秋的事
I won't speak about Rachel.
能简要和我谈谈你的工作吗
Can you talk to me about your job in general,
概括下你都负责什么样的案子
the sorts of cases you deal with in an abstract way?
如果我担心某个学生
When I'm concerned about a student,
尤其是可能涉及到犯法行为时
especially if there's possible criminal activity involved,
我必须联系地方检察官办公室
it's my duty to contact the D.A.'s office.
如果地检提出控告
Now, if the D.A. pursues charges,
那名学生就得作证指控自己的父母
the student has to testify against their own parent.
让年轻人做这样的抉择太难了
That's a difficult decision for a young person to make.
非常难
Extremely difficult.
逃跑反倒容易些
It could be easier to run away.
会面定于明天
It's set for tomorrow.
塔斯克七点半到  然后直接去白宫
Tusk lands at 7:30 and then heads straight to the White House
和总统共进晚餐
for dinner with the President.
-这在官方行程上吗  -不在
- Is it on the official schedule? - No.
-我们得写上去  -我不能那么做
- We need it to be. - Well, I can't do that.
总统特意嘱咐我别写进去
The President specifically asked that I leave it off.
实际上  好极了  我们能利用那点
Actually, that's good. We can make that work.
你能为总统和博奇安排一次会面吗
Can you set up a meeting between Birch and the President?
关于什么事
About what?
让他对总统的提名发表意见
So he can give him his two cents about who he will nominate.
我认为不该把博奇扯进来
I don't think we want Birch getting involved.
-他不会有机会的  -你有什么计划
- He'll never get the chance. - What are you planning?
今天晚些时候能安排会面吗  行不行
Can you set up a meeting for later today? Yes or no?
我会挤出时间的
I'm sure I can squeeze it in.
好  我会找博奇谈  给他打电话
Good. I'll talk to Birch. Get him on the phone.
这事得保密  就像和塔斯克的晚餐会面
This has to stay off the books, just like the dinner with Tusk.
-好的  -最后
- Okay. - And finally,
你有能开除的排程员吗
do you have a scheduler that you can fire?
弗兰克・安德伍德  查看邮箱
简宁  我有料给你
Janine, I've got something for you.
这是什么
What is this?
总统今天至周五的秘密行程
The President's O.T.R. schedule between now and Friday.
-你怎么得到的  -这不重要
- How'd you get this? - It doesn't matter.
看看他今天下午和谁见面
Look who he's meeting with this afternoon.
-鲍勃・博奇  -再看看周五晚上的
- Bob Birch. - And look at Friday night.
雷蒙德・塔斯克
Raymond Tusk.
这些见面没什么不寻常的
These aren't the craziest meetings for him to be having.
那为什么不列在官方行程里
Then why aren't they on the official schedule?
他们是副总统的候选人
He's considering them for Vice President.
这倒是个保密的好理由
I'd say that's reason enough to keep them secret.
发布出去  马上
Get this out, right away.
议长先生  我听说
Mr. Speaker, I'm hearing that
总统正考虑让你做副总统
you're gonna be considered for the Vice Presidency.
头条网报道
Slugline is reporting that
你正要前往白宫
you're heading to the White House right now.
-我  不是  -你不是去白宫吗
- I'm, uh... no. - You're not headed to the White House?
是的  总统想问我的意见
Yes. The President just wants my input.
但有可能
But there's the possibility
你自己也在考虑范围内
that you might be under consideration yourself.
据我所知不是  抱歉
Not that I'm aware of. Excuse me.
行程怎么流出去的
How did the schedule get out?
是排程办公室的人泄露的  先生
It got leaked, sir, by someone in the scheduling office.
-故意的吗  -是意外
- On purpose? - Accidentally.
附件粘进了对外的邮件里
A wrong attachment to an e-mail that went wide.
不论是谁  给我开除
Well, whoever it was, I want them out.
我已经解雇他们了
I already let them go.
-博奇还在这里吗  -他正等在外面
- Is, uh, Birch here yet? - He's waiting outside.
会面取消  告诉他临时有事
Well, cancel the meeting. Tell him something came up.
-我不想助长流言  -是的  先生
- I don't want to feed the frenzy. - Yes, sir.
请帮我接专线
Give me the private line, please.
我家街上停着三辆卫星车
There are three satellite trucks on my street.
我被困在自己家里了
I'm trapped in my own home.
是排程办公室的人闯的祸
Somebody in the scheduling office fucked up.
你真在考虑博奇
Are you seriously considering Birch?
当然没有
Absolutely not.
我们失去控制了  加勒特
We are losing control of the process, Garrett.
每次我对你诉说  你从未做出过回应
Every time I've spoken to you, you've never spoken back.
但考虑到我们互相鄙视
Although given our mutual disdain,
我不能责怪你的沉默
I can't blame you for the silent treatment.
或许我找错了对象
Perhaps I'm speaking to the wrong audience.
你听得到吗
Can you hear me?
你会说话吗
Are you even capable of language,
或是你只明白堕落
or do you only understand depravity?
彼得  是你吗
Peter, is that you?
别躲在我的脑袋里了  出来吧
Stop hiding in my thoughts and come out.
如今你死了  拿出生前没有的勇气吧
Have the courage in death that you never had in life.
出来吧  直视我的眼睛说出你想说的
Come out, look me in the eye and say what you need to say.
天堂地狱都没法给你慰藉
There is no solace above or below.
只有我们自己  渺小  孤独
Only us... Small, solitary,
奋斗  与彼此斗争
striving, battling one another.
我向自己祈祷  为自己祈祷
I pray to myself, for myself.
你好
Hello?
谁啊
Who is it?
我的律师让我不要和你说话
My lawyer said I shouldn't be talking to you.
我的也是
Mine said the same thing.
我不会改变主意的  克莱尔
I'm not gonna change my mind, Claire.
我犯了个错误  我生气了  一时冲动
I made a mistake. I got upset, and I acted impulsively.
是我犯了个错误
I was the one who made the mistake
我就不该跟你合作
by partnering with you in the first place.
好吧  那我们可以承认
Well, then, can we please both admit
事情本不该闹成这样  有平和的...
that it wasn't meant to be, and we can find an amicable way...
-不行的  -你想怎样
- No, we can't. - What do you want?
传递一个信息
To send a message.
像你这样的组织吞掉大把善款
Organizations like yours get 90% of the grant money,
再去奉承破坏环境的捐助者
then cozy up to corporate sponsors who destroy the environment.
你所说的全是谎话
The things you're claiming are lies.
我从没提及你怀孕的事
I never mentioned your pregnancy.
我和伊芙琳・巴克斯特联系过了
I got in touch with Evelyn Baxter.
记得她吗  我们聊得可久了
Remember her? We had a long conversation.
似乎你总是炒掉和你意见不一的人
It seems that you have a history of axing people who disagree with you.
她会为我作证
She'll be testifying on my behalf.
还有你让她炒掉的八个人
So will eight of the people that you made her fire.
如果你要我道歉  我就是来道歉的
If you want an apology, I'm here to offer you one,
并给你任何你认为合理的补偿
and to give you whatever you think is fair.
这案子将因为你丈夫
This case is gonna get national attention
得到全国范围的关注
because of who you're married to.
我将有机会发表自己的看法
I'll have a platform to say what I want to say.
这比你能提供的都好
That's worth more than anything you could offer.
听着  我们的确观念不同
Listen, I know we have different philosophies,
但我们的目标是一样的
but what we're trying to achieve is exactly the same thing.
我们不该相互敌对
We shouldn't be fighting each other.
感觉到了吗  胎动
Do you feel that? The kicking?
我不会让你这样的人
I won't let people like you
毁了我的孩子将居住的世界
fuck up the world my child has to live in.
如果我必须要说些谎
If I have to tell a few lies to do that...
至少我从你那儿学了件有用的东西
At least I learned one valuable thing from you.
-要点什么  -纯格兰利威
- What can I get for you? - Glenlivet, neat.
烦诉讼的事吗
The lawsuit?
还有别的事
And other things.
什么事
What other things?
我没法保证
You know, I cannot guarantee you
这一切都将成功
that all of this is gonna succeed.
不是为那个
Oh, it's not that.
说吧  不然我就一直猜下去
You can tell me, or I can keep guessing.
你会翻白眼的
You'll roll your eyes.
不会的
Not at you.
我在想我们俩谁先死了
I was thinking about when one of us dies
不管是谁先...
whether it's you first or me...
如果是我  而且肯定是我
Well, if it is me, and I'm sure it will be,
你也不会孤独太久的
you won't be alone for long.
不  我是说  我们会留下什么
No. I mean, what will we leave behind?
我们做了很多大事
We've accomplished a great deal.
我们还会有更多成就
And I intend for us to accomplish a lot more.
为了谁呢
But for whom?
为了彼此
For each other.
但如果我们不...
But if we're not...
我说傻话了
Ah, I'm being silly.
你出过书吗
Have you ever been published?
好多次了
Many times.
这问题真傻
I guess that's a stupid question.
你不像个挨饿的艺术家
You don't seem like a starving artist.
别以貌取人
Don't judge a book by its cover.
你的笑声很好听
You have a nice laugh.
-真的吗  -很有魅力
- Really? - It's very attractive.
你待在酒店吗
Are you staying at the hotel?
你想来我房间吗
You want to come up to my room?
看情况
That depends.
我要付多少钱
Well, how much would that cost me?
这些钱就差不多
That seems about right.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
伸出手
Put out your hands.
睁开眼睛
Now open them up.
我在找这个女人
I'm trying to find this woman.
如果你逼我亮出警徽
If you make me pull out my badge,
我就不得不逮捕你
I have to take you in.
但我不想那么做
But I don't want to do that.
别在这儿现眼
Let's not make a scene.
我以前常看到她
I used to see her around.
但她离开这一行了  我们没怎么联系
She left the business, though. We haven't really kept in touch.
知道她可能在哪吗
Any idea where she might be?
我的一个朋友见过她
A friend of mine saw her waiting tables
在乔治城的一家餐馆做服务员
at a restaurant in Georgetown.
我想问的问题是...
I guess the question I'm trying to ask is, um...
有必要做尝试吗
Is it even worth that step?
总的来说
The bottom line is that
对于你这个年纪的女人  会非常难
for a woman your age, it's extremely hard.
你流过产吗
Have you ever had a miscarriage?
没有  我...
No. I, um...
我有过晚的时候  但...
I've been late before, but
其实我也不能确定
I don't... You know, I don't know. I don't know exactly.
你堕过胎吗
Have you had any abortions?
三次
Three.
那就更棘手了
That can make it more difficult.
我不是在劝阻你
I'm not trying to dissuade you,
但你务必要经过深思熟虑之后再决定
but please make sure you think long and hard before you decide.
但是有可能的
But it's possible?
如果你和你丈夫符合全部标准
Assuming you and your husband fit all the criteria?
是的  可能
Yes, it's possible.
好的
Okay.
什么  这不是我的问题
What? Well, that's hardly my problem.
不  你去做就是...
No, you get on it. It's...
我一会儿打给你  什么事
I have to call you back. What is it?
桑科的股票
Sancorp's stock.
过去四个小时涨了35%
It's up 35% in the last four hours.
财经新闻上都在报道
It's all over the financial news.
塔斯克出招了
Tusk is making a play.
给雷米打电话
Get Remy on the phone.
安德伍德议员在三号线上
Congressman Underwood on line three.
我正要打电话给你
I was just about to call you.
我今晚得在总统之前见塔斯克一面
I need to meet with Tusk before he sees the President tonight.
-他已经到了  -在白宫吗
- He's already here. - At the White House?
他决定提前几小时来
He decided to come in a few hours early.
他的飞机半小时前到了
His plane landed half an hour ago.
-你知道他在哪吗  -不知道
- Do you know where he is? - I don't know.
他让自己的车去接他  我刚刚才知道
He had his own car pick him up. I just found out.
雷米不在办公室
Remy's not in his office.
我给他的办公室和手机都留了言
I left word there and on his cell.
听着  你一知道他在哪就给我打电话
Look, you need to call me the moment you know where he is.
好的
Okay.
现在只有午餐菜单  可以吗
It's just the lunch menu right now. I hope that's okay.
可以
Yeah. That's fine.
服务员马上就来招呼两位
Your server will be with you shortly.
瑞秋在吗
Is Rachel working?
不  她周日才上班
Uh, no. I don't think she's scheduled till Sunday.
今天下午是斯蒂芬妮值班
Stephanie will be with you this afternoon.
谢谢
Thanks.
我们周日再来吗
Should we come back Sunday?
我一会儿回来
I'll be right back.
打扰  有什么事吗
Excuse me. Can I help you with something?
嗯  我在找厕所
Yeah. I was just looking for the bathroom.
要不然您用办公室里的厕所
Unless you want to use the restroom in the office.
-你在给谁打电话  -瑞秋
- Who are you calling? - Rachel.
瑞秋・波斯纳吗
Rachel Posner?
我叫佐伊・巴恩斯
My name is Zoe Barnes.
我是头条网的记者
I'm a reporter at slugline.Com.
我知道彼得・罗素的事
I know about Peter Russo.
瑞秋
Rachel?
如果不想看到写你和罗素的文章  就跟我见一面
快点  瑞秋
Come on, Rachel.
你不该提罗素的
You shouldn't have mentioned Russo.
-她会回的  -要是我就不回
- She'll write back. - I wouldn't if I was her.
在哪见
你知道多少
How much do you know?
他被警察拦下时你和他在一起
That you were with him when he was pulled over.
-还有谁知道  -只有我
- Who else knows? - Just me.
我可以保密  但我要更多信息
I can keep it that way, but I need more.
-就这些了  -你撒谎
- There is no more. - You're lying.
没错  他被警察拦下时我是和他一起
Yeah, I was with him when he got pulled over.
他们带走了他  放我走了
They took him away and let me go.
我不知道他后来怎样了
I don't know what happened to him.
他没有被起诉
He was never charged.
那你知道得比我多
You know more than me, then.
没人来找过你吗
No one ever came to talk to you?
-找我干什么  -让你保持沉默
- About what? - To keep you quiet.
干那行不会到处宣扬的
You don't kiss and tell in that business.
即使与议员有关也不会吗
Not even when it's a congressman?
尤其是牵扯到议员时
Especially when it's a congressman.
弗兰克・安德伍德没有找过你吗
Frank Underwood never approached you?
他是谁
Who's that?
别跟我装傻了  瑞秋
You're too smart to play dumb, Rachel.
你明知故问
You know who that is.
名字有点耳熟
Name rings a bell.
我基本不看新闻
I try not to follow the news.
有太多熟客了
Too many familiar faces.
道格拉斯・斯坦普呢
How about Douglas Stamper?
没听说过
Never heard of him.
我知道的都告诉你了
I've told you everything I know.
我知道你爸做了什么
I know about what your father did.
如果你不帮我  我会抖出罗素的事
If you don't help me, I'll write about Russo.
我会写你是个妓女
I'll write that you were a prostitute,
还有你离家出走的原因
and I'll write about why you left home.
随你便  贱人
Go to town, bitch.
怎么样
So?
她提到了你和你的上司
She mentioned both you and your boss.
-具体点  -她没说
- What exactly? - She didn't say.
她似乎只知道
All she seemed to know was that
他酒驾被拦下时我也在车上
I was in the car with him when he got pulled over.
你没有说别的吧
And you didn't admit to more than that?
没有  我完全按你说的讲
No. I said everything exactly like you told me to.
-你真以为我会和盘托出吗  -冷静点
- You really think I'd spill my guts? - Calm down.
你为什么不告诉我他会伤害自己
Why didn't you tell me he was gonna hurt himself?
否则我绝不会那么做
I never would've done it.
我怎么知道会那样
How could I have known?
-我只希望这事快点过去  -会的
- I just want all this to go away. - It will.
都会过去的
All of it.
我保证
I promise.
要我为你订晚餐吗
Do you want me to order you dinner?
-道格在哪  -我不知道  他提早走了
- Where's Doug at? - I don't know. He left early.
-帮我联系他  -好  先生
- Call him for me, will you? - Yes, sir.
再过十三分钟
Thirteen minutes from now,
塔斯克就要和总统会面
Tusk will meet with the President,
他大概早就到了
if he isn't there already.
你从来都不是我的盟友  不是吗
You've never been an ally, have you?
缓慢坚定地向前推进
Pressing on with your slow, incessant march.
就算我不出手  时间也会杀死罗素
Time would've killed Russo if I hadn't,
有一日它也会夺去我的生命
just as it will kill me someday.
无人能逃
Kill us all.
先生  道格没接  进入语音信箱了
Sir, I just got Doug's voicemail.
不知道他在哪里
I wonder where he's at.
可能是他
Well, maybe this is him.
弗莱迪
Freddy?
抱歉  弗兰克  良禽择木而栖
Sorry, Frank. I had to trade up.
桑科是大鱼  但雷蒙德・塔斯克是巨鲸
Sancorp's a big fish, but Raymond Tusk is a whale.
想吃点什么吗  弗兰克
Can I get you something, Frank?
暂时不要  谢谢  弗莱迪
Nothing right now. Thank you, Freddy.
我不打扰你们
I'll leave y'all to it.
我希望你别介意
I hope you don't mind that
雷米告诉了我你的小秘密
Remy told me about this little secret of yours.
我想找一个你觉得舒服的地方
I wanted a place where you'd feel comfortable.
你现在不该在白宫吗
Shouldn't you be at the White House?
我怎么能错过华盛顿最好的肋排呢
How could I pass up the chance to eat the best ribs in Washington?
雷米跟你说了桑科的事
Remy told you about Sancorp.
到今天收盘时  我有3%的股份
As of closing bell today, I own 3%.
到下周末  我的股份将超过10%
By the end of next week, I'll own over ten.
足以解我后顾之忧了
Enough to make sure they can't cause me any trouble.
不过是个大胆的尝试  我很钦佩
A valiant effort, though. I respect that.
那你找我来干什么
So why are we here?
我说过会让你考虑到今天
I told you I'd give you until today to think things over.
-我是个信守承诺的人  -我还是没兴趣
- I'm a man who keeps my word. - And I'm still not interested.
在圣路易斯时  你让我详说
You wanted me to be more specific back in St. Louis.
那会是个良好的开端
That would be a good start.
英国150年前为什么对中国发动战争
Why did Britain go to war with China 150 years ago?
我没心情猜谜
I'm in no mood for riddles.
迁就我一下吧
Humor me a moment.
-鸦片  -远不止鸦片  弗兰克
- Opium. - It was bigger than opium, Frank.
那只是借口
That was simply the excuse.
中国政府不想受西方牵制  要自己做主
Peking wanted to call the shots instead of the west.
我们现在也面临着这个问题
It's the same problem we're facing now.
但人们讨厌贸易战争  更不用说军事战争了
But nobody wants a trade war, much less a military one.
你的鸦片是什么
And what's your opium?
钐149  我的反应堆需要
Samarium-149. I need it for my reactors.
中国控制了世界95%的供给
China controls 95% of the world's supply.
你在担心
And you're worried about
我们货币的不平衡  我们的外债
the imbalance in our currency, our foreign debt...
-一切  -总统已经很听你话了
- All of it. - You already have the President's ear.
贸易关税由国会控制
Trade tariffs are controlled by congress.
你在那里比加勒特更有影响力
You have a lot more influence there than Garrett does.
这也是我之前把你留在那儿的原因
It's the reason I wanted you to stay there in the first place.
那你具体要我做些什么
And what exactly would you want me to do?
我还不清楚
Well, that part I don't know yet.
得等着看中国那边的情况
We'll have to wait and see how things play out with the Chinese.
我告诉过你了  我不开空头支票
I've already told you I will not do a blank check.
我真是没想到啊  弗兰克
I must say I'm surprised, Frank.
你一向以务实闻名
You have a reputation for pragmatism.
我还不跟人签卖身契
And I also have avoided a reputation for indentured servitude.
一个提议我不说三次  弗兰克
I never make an offer more than twice, Frank.
如果你愿意合作  现在就告诉我
Tell me now if I can count on your cooperation.
你不是在提议合作  而是在要求监管
You're not offering cooperation. You're demanding tutelage.
我向你提个议吧
So let me make you a proposal.
我非常愿意与你平等合作
I am absolutely willing to work together as equals.
我会像总统一样重视你的想法
I will take your opinions seriously, just as the President does.
但我不会提前做出保证
But I will not bind myself to them in advance.
如果那不够吸引你
If that doesn't interest you, fair enough.
那就祝你能在接下来四天找到一位
Good luck finding a vice President in the next four days
和我一样务实的副总统
who will prove as pragmatic as I.
你买不到忠心  雷蒙德
You can't purchase loyalty, Raymond.
我想的那种不行
Not the sort I have in mind.
如果你想赢得我的忠心
If you want to earn my loyalty,
就得以你的忠心为交换
then you have to offer yours in return.
如果这点能达成一致
And if we can agree to that...
那么
Well,
你是个有想象力的人
you're a man with imagination.
等等
Wait.
如果斯坦普本人在那儿
If Stamper was there himself,
这就比一份消失的逮捕文件严重得多
this goes much deeper than a lost arrest file.
咱们想想
Well, let's think about this.
罗素给了他什么
What did Russo gain him?
宾州州长
A mansion in Harrisburg.
安德伍德的野心不止于此
Uh-uh. Underwood thinks bigger than that.
-那是什么  -不知道
- Then what? - I don't know.
他控制了宾州
He controls Pennsylvania.
在白宫就有影响力
He has influence in the White House.
-沃克需要这个州支持他再选  -不
- Walker needs the state for reelection... - No.
不会只是为沃克
No, it can't just be Walker.
总统在提名国务卿时出卖了他
The President backstabbed him for the secretary of state nomination.
一定是别的什么
It has to be something else.
总统欠他人情
The President would owe him.
欠他什么
But what?
他们一周见一次面
They already meet once a week.
教育法案吗  他要什么
The education bill? I mean, what?
具体要什么
What specifically?
他可能想要副总统提名
He could be after the V.P. Nomination.
但这样说不通
That doesn't make sense, though.
副总统之所以空出来  是因为罗素输了
The V.P. slot is on the table because Russo tanked.
安德伍德希望他赢
Underwood wanted him to win.
除非不是那样
Unless he didn't.
也许他希望罗素自毁前程
Maybe he wanted Russo to self-destruct.
迫使马修斯竞选
To force Matthews to run.
没错  等到下周马修斯赢得竞选时
Exactly. And then next week, when Matthews wins...
总统就会提名安德伍德
The President taps Underwood.
总统先生
Mr. President.
塔斯克先生
Mr. Tusk.
谢谢你这么快赶过来
Thanks for coming on such short notice.
请坐  弗兰克
Have a seat, Frank.
我要坦白件事
I have a confession to make.
雷蒙德和我是老相识
Raymond and I have known each other for years.
我们没让外界知道
We don't publicize it,
他一直是我可信赖的顾问
but he's been a trusted advisor to me.
我让你去圣路易斯
And I sent you to St. Louis
是为了让他了解一下你
so he could spend time with you,
给我点意见
give me his two cents.
恕我冒昧  什么意见  先生
On what, sir, if I may ask?
让你当副总统
Offering you the vice presidency.
我告诉总统  依我个人浅见
I told the president that, uh, in my humble opinion,
有你这样经验丰富  智慧忠诚的副总统
both he and the country would be well served
无论他还是国家  必会受益无穷
by a man as experienced, intelligent, and loyal as you.
我现在正式向你提出  弗兰克
So I'm officially asking, Frank.
先生  我都不知道说什么好了
Sir, I... I don't know what to say.
说好
Say yes.
好
Yes.
这真是莫大的荣幸  总统先生
It would be a great honor, Mr. President.
密查姆
Meechum.
我照顾自己人
I take care of my own,
你也证明了自己的价值
and you've proved yourself to be very valuable.
等我上任后  我希望你加入
I would like you to be part of my security detail
我是保安特遣队
once I get confirmed.
那是特勤局的范畴  先生
That's the Secret Service, sir.
我是国会警察
I'm capitol police.
那我就把你调去特勤局
Then I'll put you on the Secret Service.
如果你愿意的话
If you're interested.
我非常愿意  先生
I'd be more than interested, sir.
很好
Good.
也很感激
And I'm extremely grateful.
那就继续发挥价值
Keep being valuable.
这是表达感激最好的方式
That's the best way to show your gratitude.
我会的  副总统先生
I will, Mr. Vice President.
水管工终于来过了
Did the plumber finally come?
没有  是我修的
No. I fixed it.
弗兰西斯
Francis.
真为你骄傲  弗兰西斯
So proud of you, Francis.
不是我一个人的功劳
I didn't do it alone.
我尽快赶过来了
I got here as quickly as I could.
出什么事了吗
Is something wrong?
我要你对我说实话  克里斯蒂娜
I need you to be completely honest with me, Christina.
什么事
About what?
几天前  我曾说如果有媒体来纠缠你
The other day, when I said that you should tell me
让你告诉我
if anyone from the press started harassing you...
是佐伊・巴恩斯吗
Zoe Barnes?
你打电话说想跟我说点事
You said you wanted to talk about something on the phone.
没事  那不急
Oh, no. That can wait.
来吧  告诉我
No. Come on. Tell me.
我...今天早些时候...
I, um... earlier today...
划船机  我看见它坏了
The rowing machine, I saw, is broken.
是我搞坏的  线断了
Oh, it's my fault. The cable broke.
我还没来得及换上
I haven't been able to replace it yet.
跟我去跑步怎么样
What about going for a run with me?
她想毁谤安德伍德议员
She's trying to smear Congressman Underwood.
头条网的每个人都参与了
It's a coordinated campaign by everyone at Slugline.
但她知道些事
But she knew things.
什么事
Like what?
彼得的事
About Peter.
与科恩失去提名有关
Something to do with Kern losing the nomination.
还有吗
And?
要我开车跟着你吗  先生
Want me to drive alongside you, sir?
不用  你待在这儿
No. You stay here.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
准备好了吗
You ready?
好了
Yes.
道格・斯坦普